http://leerburg.com/privacy.htm?loc=footer

For 40+ years we've helped over 300,000 dog trainers just like you!
My Recently Viewed
Don't have an account? Sign up and get access to the features listed above and more!
Leerburg Video On Demand (VOD)
with 1537 videos
VOD Home
FAQ
Need help?
newest releases
Your Puppy 8 Weeks to 12 Months (2019)
Remote Collar Training for the Pet Owner
Foundation of Sport Detection with Ericka Duggan
View all new streams
Leerburg Online University (LOU)
How We Manage Dogs in Our Home
Get access to great lessons on how to manage a multi-dog home, participate in discussions, and earn a certificate of completion RISK FREE.
FAQ
Need help?
Newest Releases
Your Puppy 8 Weeks to 12 Months (2019)
Last updated November 27th, 2017
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. We are based in the USA.
Our principal activity is: Produce and sell dog training videos and equipment and provide dog training information. Our privacy policy covers Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. and its website.
Organization name
Leerburg Enterprises, Inc.
Address
406 Technology Drive West
City, State, Zip
Menomonie, WI 54751
Country
USA
Controller
Ed Frawley
Website
https://leerburg.com
Phone
(715) 235-6502
Newsletter Policy
Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. sends out a newsletter. The following people will receive this newsletter unless they opt-out and chose not to receive it:
Customers who purchase products from Leerburg Enterprises, Inc.
People who write and ask that one of our catalogs be sent through the United States Postal Service.
People who specifically ask to be placed in our newsletter mailing list.
People who send Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. emails with questions on dog training.
Anyone who registers for the Leerburg webboard.
Every newsletter has an opt-out option at the bottom of the newsletter. If a person does not wish to receive our newsletter, they simply click the unsubscribe link and they will automatically be added to the list of people who no longer receive our newsletters.
We do not sell our email lists or mailing lists.
I want to make it very clear that Leerburg will never sell customer information to other online data collection companies. Not ever! We have been asked many times to rent our mailing list. We will never do that, much less pass on customer information to a third party.
I take the stewardship of our customer's personal information very seriously. I don't want my personal information shared with someone who is influenced by the highest bidder, and I assume our customers feel the same way.
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our website's home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.
The Services and Links of Our Websites
Our websites do not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.
Our websites do not include links to third party web service providers.
Automatic Collection of Information
We only use cookies for our shopping cart system and webboard. They are used for the functionality of the website and are not used to track any personal information.
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.
If we wish to use your personal data for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes:
By sending an email - frawley@leerburg.com
By sending postal mail to this address - 406 Technology Drive West, Menomonie, WI 54751
By calling this telephone number - (715) 235 - 6502
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.
We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children and to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our website, we:
Do not enter information given to us by people under the age of 18 into our mailing list database.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.
Confidentiality
We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:
Primary personal data (such as name and contact details)
Identifiers (such as credit card details, website password)
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
Unauthorized access
Improper use or disclosure
Unauthorized modification
Unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Security
Leerburg Enterprises make safety of your private information a #1 priority. Where possible we put the highest safe guards on data and adhere to all industry standards on data security.
Orders are placed through a high grade 128-bit encrypted HTTPS connection. Orders are received by Leerburg over a secure, private, encrypted connection. Some information (like your email order receipt) is transferred over email, but does not contain vital information like credit card numbers, expiration dates or CVV2 Codes. Orders are processed and fulfilled by (background-checked) employees at a secure facility in Menomonie, Wisconsin. Order Records are stored digitally on a secure server with limited access (CVV2 information is not kept past processing). Paper records are securely stored for the legal number of years required per credit card company policy. Paper records do not have credit card details printed on them.
We do not store any card information past the point of processing. We are fully PCI compliant.
Access to the Personal Data We May Hold About You
Upon request, which you can indicate by:
Sending an email - frawley@leerburg.com
Sending postal mail to this address - 406 Technology Drive West, Menomonie, WI 54751
Calling this telephone number - (715) 235-6502
We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week, although we may require proof of your identity beforehand. We will provide the information without any charge.
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:
Erased
Rectified or amended
Completed
We reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. However, we allow you to challenge that decision.
Privacy Compliance
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our website or organization.
There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our website or organization.
In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are:
Voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure
Self Assessment Procedure:
Privacy Support:
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
Table of Personal Data Collected and Purposes for Which They Are Used
Volunteered by each visitor:
Other personal details and profiling data is not collected. These include data that may be volunteered by each visitor, such as:
Stay in touch! Get the latest news on products, sales, and online courses by signing up for our newsletter.
Leerburg Enterprises, Inc.
©1994 - 2020 Leerburg Enterprises, Inc.
